function() {
	var questions = {
		question: "What is NOT a horse riding discipline?",
		choices:{
			correct: "Sitting",
			wrong: ["Dressage", "Reining", "Show Jumping"]
		}
	},

	{
		question: "What is a castrated horse called?",
		choices:{
			correct: "Gelding",
			wrong: ["Stallion", "Castrated horse", "A castrate"]

	},

	{
		question: "What is the correct gait order from slowest to fastest?",
		choices:{
			correct: "Walk, Trot, Canter, Gallop",
			wrong: ["Trot, Walk, Gallop, Canter", "Walk, Canter, Trot, Callop", "Canter, Walk, Gallop, Trot"]

	},

	{
		question: "What is the name of the strap that goes under the horse’s belly so the saddle doesn’t move?",
		choices:{
			correct: "Girth",
			wrong: ["Belly strap", "Horse belt"]

	},

	{
		question: "What is the largest horse breed?",
		choices:{
			correct: "Shire",
			wrong: ["Friesian", "Clydesdale", "Belgian Draft Horse"]

	},

	{
		question: "How can you tell that horse is angry?",
		choices:{
			correct: "Ears pinned back",
			wrong: ["Growling", "Licking it's lips"]

	},

	{
		question: "What unit is most commonly used to measure a horses height?",
		choices:{
			correct: "Hands",
			wrong: ["Centimeters", "Inches", "Feet"]

	},

	{
		question: "What do you call the person that takes care and trims the horse’s hooves?",
		choices:{
			correct: "Farrier",
			wrong: ["Hoof carer", "Hoof trimmer", "Hoover"]

	},

	{
		question: "What is the proper name for the piece of equipment you put on the horses head and use it to steer with?",
		choices:{
			correct: "Bridle",
			wrong: ["Head piece", "Head gear", "The steer"]

	},

	{
		question: "What are dapples?",
		choices:{
			correct: "Round, coloured markings on the horse",
			wrong: ["Noises from a horse’s stomach", "A British term for a halter"]

	}
}];	